lanka.info 2004-06-04

# Kapruka - www.lanka.info

Privacy on this site 

What personally identifiable information is collected on this site?   
Visitors may supply personally identifiable information (such as name, address or telephone numbers) for various purposes on this site. These purposes include registering to receive e-mail newsletters, requesting further information about our products, or simply asking a question about Kapruka web site at www.lanka.info. We do not collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us. This means that you can visit our site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. 

How does this site store your credit card information?  
Kapruka will never store your credit card information. All credit card transactions are done through  
a secure link to VeriSign (the largest and most reputable e-commerce security firm).   

What anonymous information is collected on this site?  
Anonymous clickstream information is NOT collected for any visitor to this site. This includes pages viewed, date and time, and browser type. IP numbers are not stored, but are temporarily used to determine domain type and in some cases, geographic regions. 

How does this site use cookies?   
Kapruka uses session cookies for its shopping cart. If your browser's cookies are disabled then kapruka will use URL forwarding instead of cookies. Sinhala/Tamil e-mail service uses cookies for storing your last login name. If you wish to disable cookies, please goto Internet Explorer -> Tools and set the privacy setting to 'High'.

E-mail Links   
We use e-mail links located on this site to allow you to contact us directly via e-mail. We use the information provided in your e-mail to respond to your questions or comments. We may also store your comments for future reference. Your personal information is only shared with third parties with your explicit permission. 

Sinhala E-mail directory  
We will list your first name, last name, MM/DD of the birth date and country on the s-Mail member directory. However, you may prevent this by checking the 'Do not list me in s-mail' check box at the bottom of the s-mail membership application. If you are already listed on the s-mail directory, you could change your s-mail settings to hide you from the member list. 

For more information   
If you have any questions, concerns or comments, please e-mail lexingtonky.office@kapruka.com   

* * *

* * *

© 2000-2004 Kapruka - www.lanka.info - _Bringing Sri Lanka one step closer to you._
